<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Drink Chef</string>
    <string name="liquorButtonTxt">Liquor</string>
    <string name="mixerButtonTxt">Mixers</string>
    <string name="garnishButtonTxt">Garnishes</string>
    <string name="searchButtonTxt">Search</string>


    <string name="gin_and_tonic">
        You need 2 ounces gin, 4 ounces tonic water, 1 tablespoon lime juice. \n
        \n
        1. Place the ice cubes in a tall, narrow glass with the ice coming near the top. \n
        2. Pour gin, tonic water, and lime juice over the ice. \n
        3. Stir well with a long-necked spoon. Serve immediately.</string>
    <string name="mojito">
You need 1 teaspoon sugar, 10 leaves fresh mint, 1 1/2 ounces white rum, 3/4 ounce fresh lime juice, Club soda, 2 sprigs fresh mint, for garnish, 1 lime twist, for garnish.\n
        \n
1. Place sugar and mint leaves in a serving glass, and gently muddle just until the leaves release their oils. \n
        2. Fill glass with ice. Add rum and lime juice. Stir to combine. \n
        3. Top with club soda and add mint sprigs and lime twist for garnish.</string>
    <string name="the_last_word">
You need 3/4 ounce gin, 3/4 ounce fresh-squeezed lime juice, 3/4 ounce maraschino liqueur, 3/4 ounce green Chartreuse.\n
\n
        1. Combine ingredients in a cocktail shaker. \n
        2. Fill with ice, and shake briskly for 10 seconds. \n
        3. Strain into a chilled cocktail glass.</string>
    <string name="tom_collins">
You need 2 ounces gin, Juice of 1/2 a lemon, 1 teaspoon sugar, Chilled club soda.\n
\n
1. Add gin, lemon and sugar to a Collins glass and stir to dissolve sugar (you can instead use simple syrup and make the process easier). \n
        2. Fill glass with large chunks of ice and top with chilled club soda. \n
        3. Insert straw and do what comes natural.</string>
    <string name="cosmopolitan">
You need 1 1/2 ounces citrus-flavored vodka, 1/2 ounce triple sec, 1/2 ounce cranberry juice, 1/4 ounce lime juice, Orange twist, for garnish.\n
\n
1. Fill a cocktail shaker with ice. \n
        2. Add vodka, triple sec, cranberry, and lime, and shake well. \n
        3. Strain into a chilled cocktail glass. \n
        4. Garnish with orange twist.</string>
    <string name="whiskey_sour">
You need 2 ounces whiskey, 1 ounce fresh-squeezed lemon juice, 1 teaspoon sugar, 1 egg white (optional—use if you’re feeling mildly adventurous, or need a drink with a little more gravitas).\n
\n
1. Pour ingredients into a cocktail shaker, fill with ice and shake for 10 seconds (if using the egg white, give it a little extra muscle and a little extra time). \n
        2. Strain into a chilled cocktail glass, or into an ice-filled Old Fashioned glass. \n
        3. Garnish with a cherry, a slice of orange, or everything or nothing at all.</string>
    <string name="mint_julep">
You need 2 to 3 ounces bourbon, 1 teaspoon sugar, 8 to 10 leaves fresh mint, mint sprigs, crushed ice.\n
\n
1. Place the sugar and water at the bottom of a julep cup or tall glass and stir until sugar is dissolved (or speed the process by using simple syrup). \n
        2. Add the mint leaves and gently bruise with a wooden muddler or a wooden spoon. \n
        3. Take care not to overwork the mint, but swab the sides of the glass with the mint\'s aromatic oils. \n
        4. Half-fill the glass with crushed ice and add the bourbon, stirring to combine. \n
        5. Fill the glass with crushed ice and stir until the outside of the glass frosts. \n
        6. Add more crushed ice if needed to fill, and generously adorn the drink with sprigs of fresh mint. \n
        7. Serve with a short straw, so the fragrance of the mint bouquet will greet the drinker with each sip.</string>
    <string name="ramos_fizz">
You need 2 ounces gin, 1 ounce cream, 1 egg white, 1/2 ounce lemon juice, 1/2 ounce lime juice, 2 teaspoons sugar, 2-3 drops orange flower water, 1-2 ounces of club soda.\n
\n
1. Combine everything except club soda in a cocktail shaker. \n
        2. Tradition dictates that the drink be shaken very hard for at least one and preferably two full minutes with ice. \n
        3. You can cheat by either whisking the mixture with a milk-frother or whisk (or tossing a spring from a Hawthorne strainer into the shaker and using that to whip the ingredients) until foamy, and then shaking with ice for a good 20 seconds, or you can buckle down and take the fully authentic ride, while working off the calories you’ll be taking in from the cream and sugar. \n
        4. Strain into a chilled Collins glass and add an ounce or two of chilled club soda, to taste.</string>
    <string name="martini">
You need 2 ounces dry gin and 1 ounce dry vermouth. \n
\n
1. Combine ingredients in a mixing glass and fill with ice. \n
        2. Stir well to chill and strain into a chilled cocktail glass.\n
        3. Twist a piece of lemon peel over the drink and use as garnish, or, if you must, toss in an olive.</string>
</resources>
